<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>kapman.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Kapman</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Kapman</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Kapman</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Kapman</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Kapman</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Kapman</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Kapman</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKapmanxx</name>
  <summary>Pac-Man Clone</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Pac-Man-Klone</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Kloon van Pac-Man</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Klon Pac-mana</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Klon Pac-mana</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Клон гри «Пакмен»</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxPac-Man Clonexx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Kapman is a clone of the well known game Pac-Man.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Kapman is een kloon van het welbekende spel Pac-Man.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Kapman jest klonem dobrze znanej gry Pac-Man.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Kapman je klon dobre známej hry Pac-Man.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Kapman є клоном добре відомої гри «Пакмен».</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKapman is a clone of the well known game Pac-Man.xx</p>
    <p>
      You must run through the maze to eat all pills without being captured by a ghost.
      By eating an energizer, Kapman gets the ability to eat ghosts for a few seconds.
      When a stage is cleared of pills and energizer the player is taken to the next stage with slightly
      increased game speed.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">U moet door een doolhof rennen om alle pillen op te eten zonder gevangen te worden door een spook. Door een energiegever te eten krijgt Kapman de mogelijkheid spoken gedurende een paar seconden op te eten. Wanneer een niveau is ontdaan van pillen en energiegevers, zal de speler naar het volgende niveau gaan met een iets verhoogde spelsnelheid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Musisz biec przez labirynt zjadając pigułki, tak aby nie dać się złapać duchom. Po zjedzeniu energetyzatora, Kapman na kilka sekund zyskuje możliwość jedzenia duchów. Po oczyszczeniu poziomu z pigułek i energetyzatora gracz przenosi się na następny poziom z trochę szybszym tempem gry.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Musíte bežať cez bludisko a jesť pilulky bez toho, aby vás chytil duch. Ak zjete energizér, Kapman získa schopnosť jesť duchov na niekoľko sekúnd. Keď sa vyčistí bludisko od piluliek a energizérov, hráč sa presunie do ďalšej úrovne s mierne zvýšenou rýchlosťou hry.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Вам слід пройтися лабіринтом, з’їсти усі пігулки і уникнути зустрічі з привидом. Ваш герой, Kapman, може проковтнути енергетик і на декілька секунд отримати здатність самому їсти привидів. Щойно ваш герой з’їсть усі пігулки і енергетики, ви зможете перейти на наступний рівень, швидкість гри на якому буде збільшено.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxYou must run through the maze to eat all pills without being captured by a ghost. By eating an energizer, Kapman gets the ability to eat ghosts for a few seconds. When a stage is cleared of pills and energizer the player is taken to the next stage with slightly increased game speed.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kapman</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.kde.org/stable/en/kdegames/kapman/index.html</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://kde.org/images/screenshots/kapman.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
</component>
